Fight Your Way Out.
Dirty Angels is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Martin Campbell.
During the United States' 2021 withdrawal from Afghanistan, a group of female soldiers posing as medical relief
are sent back in to rescue a group of kidnapped teenagers caught between ISIS and the Taliban.
Jake, played by Eva Green.
The Bomb, played by Maria Bakalova.
Medic, played by Ruby Rose.
Malik, played by Reza Brojerdi.
Geek, played by Jojo T. Gibbs.
Shooter, played by Emily Bruni.
Dirty Angels is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by Martin Campbell, with a
script co-written by Campbell, Alissa Sullivan Haggis, and Jonas McCord.
It stars Eva Green, Maria Bakalova, Rona-Lee Shimon, Ruby Rose and Jojo T.
It was released in theaters and video on demand on December 13, 2024.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, rescue
mission, taliban, military, forced marriage.
The tone is emotional and intense.